A different kind of Hollywood love story.
Bright Lights: Starring Carrie Fisher and Debbie Reynolds is
a documentary film directed by Alexis Bloom.
An intimate portrait of Hollywood royalty featuring Debbie
Reynolds, Todd Fisher, and Carrie Fisher.
Self, played by Carrie Fisher.
Self, played by Debbie Reynolds.
Self, played by Todd Fisher.
Self (archive footage), played by Eddie Fisher.
Self, played by Griffin Dunne.
Self (uncredited), played by Billie Lourd.
Bright Lights: Starring Carrie Fisher and Debbie Reynolds (on-screen title is simply Bright Lights) is a 2016 documentary about the
relationship between entertainer Debbie Reynolds (in her final film appearance) and her daughter, actress and writer Carrie Fisher.
Following a premiere at the 2016 Cannes Film Festival, the
film was broadcast January 7, 2017 on HBO.
The film explores themes of daughter, mother, hollywood, woman director.